Guide to the Stages Theater records, 1978-2017 MS 740
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series VI: Audio / Visual recordings (boxes 36-39), 1985-2009
  - Subseries D: 2006-2009
    - "Nickel and Dimed" Selected B-Roll, 2006 (id # STAG-0064) Video, Betacam SP
    - "The Cook" Selected B-Roll, 2006 (id # STAG-0086) Video, Betacam SP
    - "The Great American Trailer Park Musical" Selected B-Roll, 2006 (id # STAG-0069) Video, VHS
    - "Nickel and Dimed" Selected B-Roll, 2006 (id # STAG-0071) Video, VHS
    - "The Connection" Houston PBS Minimum Wage, 2006 (id # STAG-0184) Video, VHS
    - "Five Course Love" Selected B-Roll, 2006 (id # STAG-0203) Video, VHS
    - "Five Course Love" Selected B-Roll, 2006 (id # STAG-0211) Video, VHS
    - "The Cook" Selected B-Roll, 2006 (id # STAG-0087) Video, Betacam SP
      This recording is a duplicate of STAG-0086 and has not been digitally preserved. Request STAG-0086 for the preserved copy, at woodson@rice.edu.
    - "The Cook" Selected B-Roll, 2006 (id # STAG-0088) Video, Betacam SP
    - "The Cook" Selected B-Roll, 2006 (id # STAG-0089) Video, Betacam SP
    - "The Cook" Selected B-Roll, 2006 (id # STAG-0090) Video, Betacam SP
    - "Altar Boyz" Show B-Roll Only, 2007 (id # STAG-0091) Video, Betacam SP
    - "American Brat" Selected B-Roll, 2007 (id # STAG-0056) Video, VHS
    - "American Brat" Selected B-Roll, 2007 (id # STAG-0196) Video, VHS
    - "American Brat" Selected B-Roll, 2007 (id # STAG-0199) Video, VHS
    - "Rounding Third" by Richard Dresser, 2008 (id # STAG-0013) Video, Betacam SP
    - "Mr. Marmalade" by Noah Haidle, 2008 (id # STAG-0019) Video, Betacam SP
    - "Lady" Selected B-Roll, 2008 (id # STAG-0177) Video, Betacam SP
    - Cinderella Copy of Rehearsal Tape, 2008 (id # STAG-0119) Audio, Cassette
    - Cinderella, 2008 (id # STAG-0137) Video, VHS
  - Subseries E: Undated
    - The Sleeping Beauty, 2009 (id # STAG-0197) Video, VHS
    - Ch II B-roll Patsy Cline, undated (id # STAG-0002) Video, Betacam
    - Always...Patsy Cline, undated (id # STAG-0003) Video, Betacam
    - Ch II Feature: Herb Remington, undated (id # STAG-0004) Video, Betacam
    - Crossing the Lines: Palestinians and Israelis speak with the Compassionate Listening Project, undated (id # STAG-0005) Video, VHS
    - Stages Production B-Roll - "Always...Patsy Cline" "Dirty Story," undated (id # STAG-0007) Video, Betacam SP
    - Jeffrey Gimble and [?] Berger, undated (id # STAG-0008) Video, VHS
    - Confronting Hate Promo, undated (id # STAG-0009) Video, VHS
    - Confronting Hate: Town Hall Meeting, undated (id # STAG-0016) Video, VHS
    - Dirty Story B-roll, undated (id # STAG-0021) Video, Betacam SP
    - Cinderella's Spanish Garden / Little Red Riding Hood, undated (id # STAG-0075) Audio, Cassette
    - KUHF / KPFT, undated (id # STAG-0077) Audio, Cassette
    - The Courage of Mandy Kate Brown / Living Art/Pinocchio 3.5, undated (id # STAG-0082) Audio, Cassette
    - In Between, undated (id # STAG-0140) Video, VHS
    - Excerpts from Earlystages Children's Theatre Productions, undated (id # STAG-0141) Video, VHS
    - Selected Soundbites, undated (id # STAG-0036) Video, Betacam SP
    - Ruben Rojas, undated (id # STAG-0042) Video, VHS
    - Weekend Network with Catfish "Hair" Ted Swindley Interview, undated (id # STAG-0043) Audio, Cassette
    - Unlabeled TEAC cassette, undated (id # STAG-0044) Audio, Cassette
    - Unlabeled Maxell cassette, undated (id # STAG-0046) Audio, Cassette
    - Always Patsy Cline Fox News Morning Show, undated (id # STAG-0059) Video, VHS
    - Act Three - Hurly Burly, undated (id # STAG-0060) Video, VHS
    - Act Two - Hurly Burly, undated (id # STAG-0063) Video, VHS
    - Community Relations, undated (id # STAG-0074) Video, VHS
    - Unlabeled TDK video, undated (id # STAG-0146) Video, VHS
    - Kyle Gary B. in Channel 2, undated (id # STAG-0148) Video, VHS
    - Fox 26 Das Barbecu, undated (id # STAG-0150) Video, VHS
    - WineFest V, undated (id # STAG-0151) Video, VHS
    - Unlabeled TDK video, undated (id # STAG-0152) Video, VHS
    - Always...Patsy Cline, undated (id # STAG-0156) Audio, Cassette
    - KTRH Office Break "Always, Patsy Cline", undated (id # STAG-0160) Audio, Cassette
    - Stages PSAs, undated (id # STAG-0161) Audio, Cassette
    - Always Patsy Cline, undated (id # STAG-0163) Audio, Cassette
    - "Patsy Cline" Revised, undated (id # STAG-0164) Audio, Cassette
    - Stages Patsy Cline, undated (id # STAG-0165) Audio, Cassette
    - Women in Mind, undated (id # STAG-0168) Audio, Cassette
    - KTRH Office Break "Stages", undated (id # STAG-0172) Audio, Cassette
    - KRTS Stages tape, undated (id # STAG-0175) Audio, Cassette
    - Part I - The Story of Stages Rough Cut, undated (id # STAG-0055) Video, VHS
    - Unlabeled VHS, undated (id # STAG-0066) Video, VHS
    - Edward Said, undated (id # STAG-0070) Video, VHS
    - Unlabeled VHS, undated (id # STAG-0073) Video, VHS
    - Sundiata the Lion King, undated (id # STAG-0181) Video, VHS
    - Transforming classrooms into learning stages, undated (id # STAG-0099) Video, VHS
    - The House I Call Love, undated (id # STAG-0102) Video, VHS
    - Song of the Open Road, undated (id # STAG-0107) Audio, Cassette
    - Seattle Repertory Theatre Work Sample B, undated (id # STAG-0195) Video, VHS
    - Literature to Life, American Place Theatre, undated (id # STAG-0111) Video, VHS
    - When Dinosaurs Ruled the World!, undated (id # STAG-0114) Audio, Cassette
    - Joe's Sequences, undated (id # STAG-0115) Audio, Cassette
    - Ball-Opening Waltz, Polka, DrumBallet, undated (id # STAG-0116) Audio, Cassette
    - 4 Songs from "Harold and The Purple Crayon", undated (id # STAG-0117) Audio, Cassette
    - The Fir Tree, undated (id # STAG-0118) Audio, Cassette
    - "Little Red" Rehearsal, undated (id # STAG-0120) Audio, Cassette
    - Gretel Without, undated (id # STAG-0121) Audio, Cassette
    - John Williams Plays Bach and Scarlatti, undated (id # STAG-0123) Audio, Cassette
    - Houston Cup Ski Show Tape #3, undated (id # STAG-0125) Audio, Cassette
    - The Little Witch of Wichita, undated (id # STAG-0126) Audio, Cassette
    - how Tape #2, undated (id # STAG-0127) Audio, Cassette
    - The Missing Heart, undated (id # STAG-0212) Video, VHS
    - Sundiata the Lion King, undated (id # STAG-0129) Video, VHS
    - Tombigee: The Spirit of the Swamp, undated (id # STAG-0214) Video, VHS
    - The Three Treasures of Buccaneer Island, undated (id # STAG-0131) Video, VHS
    - The Little Witch of Wichita, undated (id # STAG-0132) Video, VHS
    - The Firebird: A Russian Fairytale, undated (id # STAG-0217) Video, VHS
    - The Courage of Mandy Kate Brown: A Tale of the Underground Railroad, undated (id # STAG-0134) Video, VHS
    - Noonie's Masterpiece in Purple, undated (id # STAG-0136) Video, VHS
    - Saigon Water Puppet Theatre, undated (id # STAG-0138) Video, VHS
    - Missoula Children's Theatre, undated (id # STAG-0139) Video, VHS
    - Saturday Explorer Series, undated (id # STAG-0176) Video, VHS
    - Unlabeled FUJI M321SP, undated (id # STAG-0183) Video, VHS
    - Sun Motion Graphics Sample Reel, undated (id # STAG-0188) Video, VHS
    - Confronting Hate: Town Hall Meeting, undated (id # STAG-0198) Video, VHS
    - Unlabeled VHS, undated (id # STAG-0200) Video, VHS
    - Stage 25 Year Retrospective Raw footage Tapes, undated (id # STAG-0201) Video, VHS
    - Confronting Hate: Town Hall Meeting, undated (id # STAG-0207) Video, VHS
- Series VII: Early Stages children's theater (boxes 40-42), 1990-2010
  - Lucky Hightops & the Cosmic Cat Patrol: Attack of the Crab Nebula, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Grant Proposals, 1992-2000 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Early Stages Halloween Hoots, 1996 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Brochures, 1997-1998 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Brochures & play bills, 1997-2008 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Aladdin, 1998 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Sleeping Beauty, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Beauty & the Beast, 1998 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Mischief Makers, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Partners in education: corporate funding of school field trips, 1999 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Early Stages house reports, 1999-2000 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Early Stages house reports, 1999-2000 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Early Stages thank you letters, 1999-2002 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Early Stages budget notes, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - In Between, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Firebird, Kennedy Center, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Tombigee, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Southwest Festival (incl. children's plays), 2000 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Early Stages brochures, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Sunshine Kids, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Early Stages house reports, 2000-2001 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Noonie's Masterpiece in Purple, 2000-2001 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Study Guides for plays, 2000-2007 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Proposal for Summer, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Little Witch of Wichita, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Cinderella, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - HISD Teacher Workshop, 2001-2002 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Early Stages Scrapbook, 2001-2002 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - R. Bang Elementary 1st grade thank you's, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - The Courage of Mandy Kate Brown, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - The Little Witch of Wichita, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - In Between, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Alicia in Wonder Tierra, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - The Courage of Mandy Kate Brown, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - The House I Call Love, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Corpus Christi School, student thanks, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Toys Take Over Christmas, 2002-2003 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - High School Residency Program, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Play: The Toys Take Over Christmas, school performances, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Spring Woods program High School, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Pinocchio 3.5, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Snow White and Rose Red, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Sunday Gold, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Play: About Being 8, school performances, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Play: Pinocchio 3.5, school performances, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Toys Take Over Christmas, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Play: How Anansi Came to America, school performances, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - About Being 8, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - How Anansi Came to America, 2005 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Teaching with the Crucible, 2005 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Peter and the Wolf, 2005 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Peter and the Wolf, 2005 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Manzi: The Adventures of Young Cesar Chavez, 2005 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Surround, 2005 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Pecos Bill and the Ghost Stampede, 2006 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Toys Take Over Christmas, 2006-2007 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Actor's Studio at YES Prep, 2007 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - The Giver, 2007 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - DePelchin ArtReach, 2008 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Teen Dating Violence, 2008 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Panto Cinderella, 2008 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Early Stages Brochures, 2009-2010 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Young Audiences: Arts for Learning Curriculum (2), 2009 (Box 42, Folder 15-16)
- Series VIII: Press and marketing (boxes 43-45), 1980-2006
  - Sub-Series A: Newsletters, 2002-2005
    - Fall 2002 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Spring 2003 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Fall 2003 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Winter 2003 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Spring 2004 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Winter 2004 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Spring 2005 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series B: Brochures, 2000-2003
    - Brochure Drafts, 2000-2001 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Early Stages Brochures, 2001-2002 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Early Stages Brochures, 2002-2003 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Main Stage Brochures, 2001-2002 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Main Stage Brochures, 2002-2003 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series C: Performance-specific Marketing, 1980-2006
    - Marco Polo Sings a Solo / After the Rain, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Miss Margarida's Way releases, 1982 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Sister Mary Ignatius, 1983 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - Beyond Therapy - News Release, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - Dedication Ceremony - Press Releases, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - 1985 releases (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - Leader of the Pack, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - Leader of the Pack Artwork, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - Ted Swindley - Lantz Office, 1988-1989 (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - "One Woman...A million laughs", 1989 (Box 43, Folder 22)
    - Artwork, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 23)
    - Artwork: Alley Benefit, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 24)
    - 1991 Releases (Box 43, Folder 25)
    - Burras Finas / There Comes a Time, 1999 (Box 43, Folder 26)
    - The Dying Gaul, 1999 (Box 43, Folder 27)
    - Full Gallop, 1999 (Box 43, Folder 28)
    - I Love you, you're perfect, now change!, 1999 (Box 43, Folder 29)
    - Anton in Show, 2000 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Company, 2000 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Douglas Mitchell Playfest, 2000 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Firebird, The, 2000 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - God's Man in Texas, 2000 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - In Between, 2000 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Memory of Water, 2000 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Refuge, 2000 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Tamalalia, 2000 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Tombigee, 2000 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Toys Take Over Christmas, 2000 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Turn of the Screw, 2000 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Communicating Doors, 2000-2001 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Betty's Summer Vacation, 2001 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Car Pool / Lew Temple benefit, 2001 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Cinderella, 2001 (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Courage of Mandy Kate Brown, 2001 (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - Elizabeth Rex, 2001 (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - Heart of a Woman, 2001 (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - The Little Witch of Wichita, 2001 (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - Noonie's Masterpiece in Purple, 2001 (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - Old Wicked Songs, 2001 (Box 44, Folder 22)
    - The Pavilion, 2001 (Box 44, Folder 23)
    - Romance & Romance, 2001 (Box 44, Folder 24)
    - Runt of the Litter, 2001 (Box 44, Folder 25)
    - The Toys Take Over Christmas, 2001 (Box 44, Folder 26)
    - Blind Faith, 2001-2002 (Box 44, Folder 27)
    - The Firebird, 2001-2002 (Box 44, Folder 28)
    - The House I Call Love, 2001-2002 (Box 44, Folder 29)
    - Marketing, 2001-2002 (Box 44, Folder 30)
    - Press releases (Main Stage, Early Stages, other, external), 2001-2002 (Box 44, Folder 31)
    - Alicia in Wonder Tierra, 2002 (Box 44, Folder 32)
    - Blood Wedding, 2002 (Box 44, Folder 33)
    - The Courage of Mandy Kate Brown, 2002 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - The Drawer Boy, 2002 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Full Gallop, 2002 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Jacob Marley's Christmas Carol, 2002 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - The Laramie Project, 2002 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Lobster Alice, 2002 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Syncopation, 2002 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - News Releases, 2002-2003 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - The Toys Take over Christmas, 2002-2003 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Bat Boy, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - The Big Voice: God or Merman?, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Dirty Blonde, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Good Boys, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Recent Tragic Events, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Snow White & Rose Red, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Speaking in Tongues, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Sunday Gold, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - Main Stage Descriptions, 2003-2004 (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - Main Stage Season Campaign, 2003-2004 (Box 45, Folder 19)
    - Always...Patsy Cline, 2004 (Box 45, Folder 20)
    - Bright Ideas, 2004 (Box 45, Folder 21)
    - Convenience, A New Musical, 2004 (Box 45, Folder 22)
    - Dirty Story, 2004 (Box 45, Folder 23)
    - Pinocchio 3.5, 2004 (Box 45, Folder 24)
    - The Toys take Over Christmas, 2004 (Box 45, Folder 25)
    - Donor Opportunities, 2006 (Box 45, Folder 26)
- Series IX: Oversize (box 46), 2012 and undated
  - Panto: Mother Goose Posters (5), 2012-11-20-2013-01-06 (Box 46)
  - 2 Pianos, 4 Hands Posters (4), 2012-09-05-2012-10-28 (Box 46)
  - Winter Wonderettes Posters (5), 2012-11-07-2012-12-30 (Box 46)
  - Negative of Stages Theater building drawing (Box 46)
  - Architectural Drawings of Stages Theater Building (3) (Box 46)
  - Picture of Stages Theater Building (Box 46)
- Series X: Computer disks
  - Subseries A: Content captured from disks
    - Stages Theater records: Financial records and mailing list
    - Stages Theater records: Various contact information
    - Stages Theater records: List of corporate donors, mailing list, letter, press release
    - Stages Theater records: Stages/Houston Symphony fliers, radio scripts, financial documents
    - Stages Theater records: "Tango" production bios
    - Stages Theater records: Houston Symphony subscription letters
    - Stages Theater records: Stages brochure images
    - Stages Theater records: Stages promotional image
    - Stages Theater records: Stages promotional material
    - Stages Theater records: Stages donation documents
    - Stages Theater records: Stages promotional material and newsletter outline
    - Stages Theater records: Stages promotional material and correspondence
    - Stages Theater records: Stages mailing lists
    - Stages Theater records: Stages correspondence, promotional materials, and budgeting documents
    - Stages Theater records: Stages correspondence, press releases, and marketing materials
    - Stages Theater records: "The Drunkard" show reports
    - Stages Theater records: Stages mailing lists and subscription letters
    - Stages Theater records: "The Story of Stages" film
    - Stages Theater records: "An Infinite Ache" selected B-roll
    - Stages Theater records: Photos from "Silence"
    - Stages Theater records: Photos from "Speaking in Tongues"
    - Stages Theater records: Photos from "Big Voice" and "Pinocchio 3.5"
    - Stages Theater records: Music from "Snow White and Rose Red"
    - Stages Theater records: Radio spot for "Baby"
    - Stages Theater records: Music from "Convenience"
    - Stages Theater records: Radio spot for "Dirty Blonde"
    - Stages Theater records: Radio spot for "Convenience"
    - Stages Theater records: Photos from "Honky Tonk Angels"
    - Stages Theater records: Photos from "Nickel & Dimed"
    - Stages Theater records: Cast photos from "Nickel & Dimed"
    - Stages Theater records: Photos from "Searching for Eden"
    - Stages Theater records: Photos from "An Infinite Ache"
    - Stages Theater records: "Title of Show" soundtrack
    - Stages Theater records: Young Artists Conservatory photos
    - Stages Theater records: "Honky Tonk Angels" soundtrack
    - Stages Theater records: "Stages: An Oral History Act I" video
    - Stages Theater records: "Stages: An Oral History Act II" video
    - Stages Theater records: "Stages: An Oral History Act III" video
    - Stages Theater records: 25th Anniversary Gala video
    - Stages Theater records: "Story of Stages Act VI" video
    - Stages Theater records: "Stages: An Oral History Act IV" video
    - Stages Theater records: "The Story of Stages" video
    - Stages Theater records: "The Dead Guy" small photos
    - Stages Theater records: "The Dead Guy" large photos
    - Stages Theater records: "Silence" footage
    - Stages Theater records: Stages Kids Show photos
    - Stages Theater records: Gala photos
    - Stages Theater records: "Altar Boyz" soundtrack
    - Stages Theater records: Board photo
    - Stages Theater records: "The Front Row" audio
    - Stages Theater records: "Always...Patsy Cline" songs
    - Stages Theater records: "Orange Flower Water" photos
    - Stages Theater records: "Searching for Eden" photos
    - Stages Theater records: "Polish Joke" photos
    - Stages Theater records: "An Infinite Ache" photos
    - Stages Theater records: "Lobster Alice" photos
    - Stages Theater records: "Communicating Doors" photos
    - Stages Theater records: "Silence" photos
    - Stages Theater records: "Bat Boy" photos
    - Stages Theater records: "Bright Ideas" photos
    - Stages Theater records: 25th Anniversary Gala photos
    - Stages Theater records: "Dog Opera" radio ad
    - Stages Theater records: "Funny Girl" radio ad
    - Stages Theater records: "Chili Queen" radio ad
    - Original discs and analysis sheets for captured content (Box 47, Folder 1, Box 48, Folder -)
  - Subseries B: Content printed from discs
    - Press releases and season notes, 1995-2000 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Subseries C: Documentation on discs with uncaptured content
    - 3.5" floppy discs with irrelevant content or that are empty (Box 47, Folder 3-4)
    - Zip discs which could not be browsed or accessed (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Subseries D: External hard drives for Stages audio/video
    - External hard drives for Stages audio/video, including mezzanine master video files, 2018; 8.3 Terabytes (Box 48)
      These external hard drives were provided by the vendor who digitized the content, Scene Savers. They include avi mezzanine master files and mp4 access files for the video, and wav and mp3 files for the audio. The audio files (both wav and mp3) and the access quality video (mp4) have been preserved in the Woodson's nearline environment as AIP numbers MS740aip_064 through MS740aip_071. All the recordings are described in this finding aid, at the item level, as Series VI.
- Series XI: Addendum (boxes 49-105)
  - Sub-Series A: Seasons (boxes 49-54)
  - Sub-Series B: Administration and Board records (boxes 55-68)
  - Sub-Series C: Development (boxes 69-87)
  - Sub-Series D: Events (boxes 88-91)
  - Sub-Series E: Audio / Visual recordings (box 92)
  - Sub-Series F: Early Stages and Young Actors Conservatory (YAC) (boxes 93-101)
  - Sub-Series G: Press and Marketing (boxes 102-105)